It seems Miss Tang
not only plays the pipa well,
but is also extremely smart.
I still have to thank you, Prince Yu.
Thanks to your decoy plan,
I was able to escape.
When I sent you the message,
I thought you wouldn't act on impulse.
I didn't expect it to go so smoothly.
Where are we going?
I'll take you out of the city first.
I have a manor in the suburbs.
You can hide there for a few days
to lay low.
I have no way to repay your great kindness, Your Highness.
I can only pray for your health and success every day.
You're too kind.
You consider me a soulmate.
How could I just ignore you?
If Miss Tang needs anything in the future,
just ask.
I will definitely grant your request.
Hyah!
Your Highness, someone is coming.
I'll go back with them.
I can't implicate you.
If we fight to the death,
we might have a chance.
Sixth Brother, you came so fast.
Did you know Miss Tang and I were leaving the city
and came to see us off?
Miss Tang,
remember I said I would grant any request.
You really are my good sixth brother.
It's getting late.
Please go back, Your Highness.
You want me to leave so you can find Yuwen Jia.
And have him help you escape again, right?
I wouldn't dare.
You wouldn't dare? What wouldn't you dare to do?
Faking your death to escape.
And standing with him.
Your Highness seems to have never heard me play the pipa.
How about this?
I will play a tune for Your Highness today.
What a great poem, 'Going out to the Frontier'.
You mean you want me to let you go home.
Since Your Highness understands my meaning,
why can't you grant my wish?
Don't even think about it.
I finally got you back.
I won't let you leave so easily again.
Isn't this face what Your Highness likes?
I will destroy it today,
so Your Highness won't desire it anymore.
Let's talk it over.
Don't hurt yourself.
If I don't hurt myself,
should I just let you hurt me?
No.
It's not like that.
Just because of this face.
To satisfy your perverted desires
and comfort your dark longing.
Are you going to take in all the women in the world
as long as they look like her,
and trample on them at will?
What on earth are you talking about?
No wonder he said those inexplicable things that day.
He knew you were right there.
He was trying to drive a wedge between us.
Prince Yu treats me with sincerity.
Unlike you.
I don't trust him.
Should I trust you?
Zhiluo.
Are you treating the target as Miss Tang
or Yuwen Jia?
I really can't stand you people trapped by love.
It's better to be free and alone.
Why are you so talkative today?
Have the accounts from the 13 families in the northwest been collected?
There was internal strife in Rouran,
so it was delayed.
I was just about to go there myself.
Speaking of Miss Tang,
it's only been two years,
but her temper and disposition are completely different.
If it weren't for the birthmark as proof,
I really wouldn't believe they are the same person.
You see, this Miss Tang,
she had such a good temper when she was a female physician,
but you didn't know how to cherish her.
Are you happy now?
You gave it all back, didn't you?
You deserve it.
What's wrong with you?
Zhiluo.
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't slipped,
you wouldn't have...
Wouldn't have what?
I'm sorry. I lost control.
Don't stay behind me anymore.
I'm afraid you'll be in danger.
Psycho.